## Sebastian Casallas Arias

Colombia, Bogotá · https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastian-casallas-arias-a46645302 · +57 3224729356· sebastiancasallasarias2020@gmail.com

Junior Software Developer with over 6 months of experience in Full Stack and FrontEnd development. I have worked on projects such as SASS platforms for veterinarians and team management using technologies like Node.js, Express, React, and TailwindCSS. I excel in implementing clean code architectures and strict typing, ensuring software quality and scalability. Additionally, I have a B2 level in English and a strong passion for continuous learning.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zecsba - APV Colombia, Bogotá May - 2024 - Present FullStack Developer

- Developed a platform to manage patients for each veterinarian in the area, achieving a 20% improvement in patient management efficiency. Used clean code architecture to prevent future issues when changing dependencies or databases.
- Implemented Model View Controller using Node.js and Express, improving code readability and reducing development time by 15%.
- Utilized React and TailwindCSS for Frontend development.

Zecsba - UpTask Colombia, Bogotá FullStack Developer June – 2024 - Present

- Developed a platform for team management for small and medium-sized companies in the sector.
  - Implemented strict typing for both Backend and Frontend to avoid execution errors.

**Academlo - Ecommerce** 

Colombia, Bogotá June – 2024 – June 2024 FrontEnd Developer

- Developed a virtual store with authentication for purchasing items.
  - Used React for the Frontend, consuming an educational API.

## **EDUCATION**

Academlo Colombia, Bogotá

FullStack Developer March 2024

Honors: Top 3 in React module

Milestones Education Australia, Melbourne

Course Intensive English B2 January 2023 - March 2024

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, TailwindCSS, clean code architecture, strict typing.
- **Soft Skills:** Time management, teamwork, effective communication, adaptability, flexibility, self-learning, Leadership.